The Deeper You Go, The Clearer It Gets
Crystal River is a drama, romance film directed by Brett Levner.
The story is of a married woman who, grieving her inability to have children,
finds comfort and healing in her friendship with another man.
It's about discovering grace in darkness and the
unexpected places we find healing.
Clay Arrendal, played by Sean Patrick Flanery.
Davie Nance, played by Emily Carpenter.
Olin Arrendal, played by Ted Manson.
Paul Nance, played by Robert Pralgo.
Rev. Nathan Hape, played by Daniel Burnley.
Rev. Alex Grayson, played by Brandon O'Dell.
Crystal Lynn Bernard (born September 30, 1961) is a retired American singer-songwriter and actress, best known for her
roles as Helen Chappel-Hackett on the sitcom Wings (1990–1997), Amy on It's a Living (1985–1989), and K.C.
Cunningham on Happy Days (1983–1984).
The tone is dark and emotional.